<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LFT - DTU</string>
    <string name="about_us">Leaders for Tomorrow(LFT) is a not-for-profit youth movement established in india
        whose members mainly consist of college students between the ages 18 and 25.\n\n The DTU chapter of LFT was
        established in August 2015, with a mission to provide a platform where the youth can express their views,
        generate ideas, meet great leaders, learn new skills, take up social action and ignite the leader in them.\n\n
        We beleive that together we can usher in a great future for our nation if we work hand in hand to bring real social change.</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="events">"Igniting Young Minds" is a project undertaken to motivate college going youth to give 1 hour of their week to under privileged students at government schools and slum kids.\nWeekly programmes include social activities like cleanliness drives, adopt a plant, shramdaan, visit for passion and cultural competitions. \nFor more details, visit <a href="http://www.lft.org.in">www.lft.org.in</a></string>
    <string name="fblink">You can message, follow and like us at <a href="http://www.facebook.com/lftdtu">www.facebook.com/lftdtu</a> or email us:</string>
    <string name="team">LFT-DTU is a team of 139 members, determined to learn and spread an aptitude for Leadership. The turnout increases with every event we carry out! \nThough we all are \"one among many\", but to organise and manage all events, we have a dedicated team as follows:</string>
    <string name="associates">Shweta Chaudhary\n2nd year,ENE\n\nShivani Sazawal\n2nd year,COE\n\nAashna Srivastava\n1st year,PCT\n\nAnanyah Dhawan\n1st year,ME\n\nArjun Singh\n1st year,ME\n\nMahitha\n1st year,ME\n\nShivam Tandon\n1st year,MCE\n\nTwinkle Singh\n1st year,SOE</string>
    <string name="sdp">We, at LFT-DTU, also focus on developing the all round personality of all our members. Along with on field experience, we also organise regular workshops and interaction sessions. These skill development sessions include training in leadership skills, communication skills, public speaking, team effort and planning.</string>
    <string name="iym">This life skill program of LFT is soon going to be launched in our college. We plan to send 10 of our volunteers, every week, to nearby slums and old age homes. Our volunteers would enlighten the children aged 6-12 belonging to lower socio- economic strata on various topics like sanitation, moral sciences, GK, englishspeaking skills etc. We will also be providing them with some basic technical knowledge related to computers. This will help our volunteers to strengthen their skills and also awaken their social consciousness. Thus with the help of these small steps we can contribute to the growth of our nation.</string>
    <string name="shramdan">It means social service in the society and community for its development. Its a combination of words shram-labour and daan-contribution. It is basically the non- monetary contribution to the society</string>
    <string name="collectiondrives">We conduct collection drives to bridge the gaps between haves and the have nots. One can collect books, clothes etc and provide them to the underprivileged.</string>
    <string name="cleanathon">Its said that cleanliness is next to godliness and to reinforce this age old adage this campaign has been launched. It is a symbolic effort aimed at reviving the consciousness towards the environment by solving the problem of littering and a myriad of its consequences</string>
    <string name="adapt">Adopt a plant is the green initiative of LFT - DTU aimed at making the youth realize the importance of our mother earth and curb global warming. This program will help the students to develop an ownership about our environment</string>
    <string name="adar">Owing to the changing social scenario and media influence, a large section of the youth are being drawn into substance abuse and ragging just to appear cool. Thus to make a sustained impact on this situation through ADAR we would encourage them to have discussions on issues like alcoholism, smoking , drug abuse and ragging so that they can understand the side effects of these menaces and avoid them</string>
</resources>
